Guide to Speeches in the Records of the Office of the President (Dr. John Brademas) RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Remarks at a faculty meeting of the School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions, NYU, 18 December 1989 (Box 624, Folder 69)
  - Remarks delivered at a Carnegie Council breakfast (NYC), 19 December 1989 (Box 624, Folder 70)
  - A Tribute to Arthur Lehning, NYU, December 1989 (Box 624, Folder 71)
  - Message from the President, staff handbook, NYU, January 1990 (Box 624, Folder 72)
  - Dinner honoring Lord and Lady Briggs, NYU, 5 January 1990 (Box 624, Folder 74)
  - "Rebuilding the Public Service," delivered before a meeting of the members of the NY Regional Office of GAO (NYC), 17 January 1990 (Box 624, Folder 75)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Community Service/Youth Service, NYU, 18 January 1990 (Box 624, Folder 76)
  - "Challenge for the 1990s: Reforming America's Public Schools," Texaco Roundtable Luncheon, 18 January 1990 (Box 624, Folder 77)
  - Remarks delivered at a USA Today Luncheon, 19 January 1990 (Box 624, Folder 78)
  - "Due Case, Una Tradizione," delivered at the second annual New York/Italy Medical Symposium (NYC), 20 January 1990 (Box 624, Folder 79)
  - Keynote address delivered at a meeting of the Global Affairs Institute, 21 January 1990 (Box 624, Folder 80)
  - "Why Support Higher Education: Making Our Case In the 1990s," delivered at a meeting of the CASE Middle Atlantic District II (NYC), 22 January 1990 (Box 624, Folder 81)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon meeting of the Faculty Resource Network, NYU, 25 January 1990 (Box 624, Folder 82)
  - Remarks delivered at an alumni reception (Boca Raton, FL), 1 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 84)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring the Real Estate Institute and Klara Silverstein, NYU, 6 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 85)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate Report, NYU, 8 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 86)
  - "An Evening in Celebration of American Musical Theatre," delivered at a dinner honoring Celia Farris (Palm Beach, FL), 10 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 87)
  - Response to University of Oklahoma Press, 15 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 88)
  - Remarks delivered at a reception for alumni (Chicago, IL), 18 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 89)
  - "Media and Local Politics," delivered at an Urban Research Center Lunch, NYU, 20 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 90)
  - Press conference announcing the grantees of the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation's "Fighting Back" Program (Washington, D.C.), 21 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 91)
  - Essays for a book honoring benefactors of NYU, 21 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 92)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring the Riklis family, 22 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 93)
  - Op-ed for The Chronicle of Higher Education, 23 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 94)
  - Remarks delivered at NYU in Albany Day, 27 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 95)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a reception honoring Chancellor Joseph Fernandez, NYU, 28 February 1990 (Box 624, Folder 96)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon benefiting Metro Center (NYC), 1 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 97)
  - Transcript of "The Congress and the Presidency," delivered at the White Burkett Miller Center, 1 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 98)
  - Remarks delivered upon receiving the Athenagoras Human Rights Award, Annual Archons Banquet, 3 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 99)
  - Remarks delivered at Sunday at the Square, NYU, 4 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 100)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon at the National Institute of Social Sciences (Cambridge, MA), 5 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 101)
  - Brief remarks delivered at a United Way/NYU Community Fund Campaign reception, 7 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 103)
  - Remarks delivered at a special academic convocation honoring Prime Minister Andreotti of Italy, 8 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 104)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate Report, NYU, 8 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 105)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon celebrating the Hagop Kevorkian Center, NYU, 9 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 106)
  - Remarks at the presentation of the John Jay Award to McGeorge Bundy (Albany, NY), 12 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 107)
  - Charles Waldo Haskins Award Dinner, 13 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 109)
  - Remarks delivered at a conference sponsored by the Ditchley Foundation (Austin, TX), 16-17 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 110)
  - Remarks delivered at the Conference on Czech Literature and Culture, NYU, 19 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 111)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring Ambassador Santamaria, NYU, 19 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 112)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Sussmuth, NYU, 19 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 114)
  - Remarks delivered at the Conference on US-USSR Cooperation at the UN, NYU, 20 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 115)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring Sir Raymond Hoffenberg, NYU, 21 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 116)
  - Remarks delivered at the Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner (NYC), 21 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 117)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a Faculty Council luncheon, NYU, 22 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 118)
  - Talking points for remarks made at a dinner honoring NYU trustees (NYC), 22 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 119)
  - Speech delivered during his induction as an Honorary Member of the Institute of International-Public Law & International Relations (Thessaloniki, Greece), 28 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 120)
  - Speech delivered before the Propeller Club & Association of Friends of Anatolia, Greece, 29 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 121)
  - Memorandum on the budget for the NYU community, 29 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 122)
  - "Salute To Benefactors of NYU Luncheon", 18 March 1990 (Box 624, Folder 123)
  - Laudatio of Ailton Krenak, 5 April 1990 (Box 624, Folder 124)
  - CASH Luncheon, 12 April 1990 (Box 624, Folder 125)
  - JB on reading, 12 April 1990 (Box 624, Folder 126)
  - Senate Report, 12 April 1990 (Box 624, Folder 127)
  - Urban Research Center Lunch, 17 April 1990 (Box 624, Folder 128)
  - Reception at Metropolitan Club, 17 April 1990 (Box 624, Folder 130)
  - Remarks delivered at the Salute to Benefactors of NYU Luncheon, 18 April 1990 (Box 624, Folder 131)
  - Olive Branch Awards Luncheon, 20 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254717
  - African Forum on the Economies of Southern Africa, 20 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 2)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 22 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square Park "Spruce Up", 24 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 4)
  - NYU Creative Writing Program Benefit, 25 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 5)
  - Sotirhos Luncheon, 25 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 6)
  - 25-Year Service Awards, 26 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 7)
  - Annual Survey of American Law Tribute, 26 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 8)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the League of Woman Voters in the City of NY, 26 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 9)
  - Young Audiences 20th Annual National Conference Lunch, 27 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 10)
  - African-American and Latino Awards Ceremony, 27 April 1990 (Box 625, Folder 11)
  - Brief statement on 25th anniversary of the Older Americans Act, 1 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 12)
  - Quotations given for an article published in the NYU business magazine, 1 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 13)
  - Article for The Chronicle of Higher Education, 1 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 14)
  - Informational Chat with President Endara of Panama, 2 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 15)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Initiation, 2 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 16)
  - 25th anniversary of the inauguration of Lyndon Baines Johnson, 3 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 17)
  - Convocation for Fritz John of the Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 9 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Council Award Dinner, 9 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 20)
  - Presentation of checks to the NYU Community Fund, 9 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 21)
  - Urban Research Center Conference, 10 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 22)
  - Statement endorsing Tim Roemer for Congress, 11 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 23)
  - 19th Annual Michiana Prayer Breakfast, 11 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 24)
  - Luncheon to honor Prof. Angelos Angelopoulos, 14 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 25)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions Valedictory Ceremony, 14 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 27)
  - Friends of Wagner School Dinner, 15 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 28)
  - Dinner for NFL Commissioner Paul Tagliabue, 15 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 29)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, 16 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 31)
  - Medical School Last Day Exercises, 17 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 32)
  - Honorary Degree Citations, 17 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 33)
  - Remarks delivered at the 158th annual commencement exercises, NYU, 17 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 34)
  - Albert Gallatin Medalist, 17 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 35)
  - Alumni Commecement Breakfast, 17 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 36)
  - Cyprus-American Association, 28 May 1990 (Box 625, Folder 37)
  - Groundbreaking for the biomolecular building at the Medical Center, 5 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 38)
  - Creative Arts Team 15th anniversary celebration, 4 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 39)
  - Dinner celebrating groundbreaking at the Medical Center, NYU, 5 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 40)
  - First meeting of the Independent Commission, 7 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 41)
  - College of Dentistry graduation ceremony, 12 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 42)
  - 21st Century Club inaugural dinner, 12 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 43)
  - Reception for the La Maison Francaise Advisory Board, 13 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 44)
  - C. Walter Nichols Award, 13 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 45)
  - Message to the International Association of Permanent Representatives to the United Nations, 13 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 46)
  - Values/Resources, 18 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 47)
  - "Global Responsibilities and National Interests," delivered at Depauw University (Greencastle, IN), 18 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 48)
  - Groundbreaking ceremony and reception for Stern, 20 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 49)
  - Management Education Center, undated (Box 625, Folder 50)
  - Independent Commission, 2nd meeting, 25 June 1990 (Box 625, Folder 51)
  - Opening remarks delivered at the 30th Biennial Clergy-Laity Congress Opening Luncheon (Washington, D.C.), 9 July 1990 (Box 625, Folder 52)
  - Remarks delivered at the Grand Banquet Honoring His All Holiness, Patriarch Dimitrios (NYC), 15 July 1990 (Box 625, Folder 53)
  - Letter to Korean Student Association, 18 July 1990 (Box 625, Folder 54)
  - Open mind interview, 29 July 1990 (Box 625, Folder 55)
  - Graduation ceremony for Metro's Center's Upward Bound program, 10 August 1990 (Box 625, Folder 56)
  - Interview with Crain's Business, 10 August 1990 (Box 625, Folder 57)
  - Reception for Harvey Stedman, 5 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 58)
  - Dedication of the William R. Salomon House, 17 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 59)
  - Presentation of Keogh Awards at an Alumni Federation Dinner, 18 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 61)
  - Reception at the Greek Consul General's residence, 18 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 62)
  - Regency Breakfast Meeting of the Executive Development Committee, 18 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 63)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Sir Richard Southwood, NYU, 20 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 64)
  - Luncheon celebrating the naming of the John J. Creedon House, 24 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 65)
  - Announcement of the Sanwa Bank Endowment, 26 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 66)
  - Remarks at a dinner honoring Sheldon Solow and the Institute of Fine Arts, NYU, 26 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 67)
  - Remarks delivered at a memorial service for Dr. Ivan L. Bennett, Jr., NYU, 27 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 68)
  - Women's Campaign Fund Dinner, 27 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 69)
  - Remarks delivered at a convocation honoring Toshiki Kaifu, NYU, 28 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 70)
  - Meeting with a visiting committee for the Wagner Graduate School of Public Service, 28 September 1990 (Box 625, Folder 71)
  - Welcome remarks delivered during a visit by President Chamorros of Nicaragua, 1 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 72)
  - Remarks delivered at a convocation honoring Carlos Salinas, NYU, 1 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 73)
  - Letter to Representative Augustus Hawkins, 1 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 74)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, 4 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 75)
  - Testimony on archives, 4 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 76)
  - The open mind, 6 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 77)
  - Tim Roemer campaign remarks, 6 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 78)
  - Remarks at the consecration of the Church of St. Andrew (South Bend, IN), 6 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 79)
  - Keynote address at a meeting of the NY State Association of Foreign Language Teachers (Kiamesha Lake, NY), 7 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 80)
  - Humanities Council symposium, 10 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 81)
  - Humanities Council symposium dinner, 10 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 82)
  - Dinner for Preston Robert Tisch, 11 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 83)
  - Remarks delivered at the Harvard Class of '49 Dinner & Panel, 12 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 84)
  - Conference on Fiscal Reform in New York State, 16 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 86)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Ahmet Ertegun Dinner, NYU, 16 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 88)
  - Interfaith Forum of NY State Religious Leaders (Rye, NY), 17 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 89)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, 17 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 90)
  - Remarks on the dedication of the Nordoff Robbins Music Therapy Clinic, 18 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 91)
  - Interview on the Comprehensive Child Development Bill of 1971, 19 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 92)
  - Burger King Honors Excellence in Education Symposium, 23 October 1990 (Box 625, Folder 93)
  - Letter to Professor Sam Proctor of the University of Florida, 1 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 95)
  - Reflections on education, 1 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 96)
  - Milton Petrie lecture & dinner, 1 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 97)
  - Op-ed on term limits, 2 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 98)
  - NY Alliance Teachers Award Luncheon, 2 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 99)
  - Luncheon commemorating the Health & Policy Management chair, 6 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 100)
  - New York magazine article, 6 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 101)
  - 4th annual All-University Dinner Dance, 7 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 103)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 8 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 104)
  - Remarks delivered at the Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture and dinner, NYU, 8 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 105)
  - Remarks delivered before students enrolled in "American Colleges" in the School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions, 12 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 106)
  - Dedication of Casa Italiana, 12 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 107)
  - Trustee Scholars Reception, 12 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 108)
  - "Jimmy Carter: Keeping Faith," delivered at a conference on Jimmy Carter at Hofstra University, 14 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 109)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring David Laventhol sponsored by the Anti-Defamation League, 14 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 110)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the American Association of University Students, 15 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 111)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring members of the Board of Trustees of the Alexander S. Onassis Public Benefit Foundation, NYU, 16 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 112)
  - Remarks delivered at the presentation of the Alexander S. Onassis Center Gold Medal for Excellence in Hellenic Studies to Professor Robert Browning, NYU, 16 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 113)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring members of the Union of Greek Shipowners and conference participants, NYU, 17 November 1990 (Box 625, Folder 114)
  - Conference on "The Greeks & The Sea," NYU, 16-18 November 1990 (Box 626, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254725
  - "Education, Culture and Philanthropy: New Challenges for the New Europe," delivered at the Residencia de Estudiantes (Madrid, Spain), 27 November 1990 (Box 626, Folder 2)
  - 50th Anniversary of Federico Garcia Lorca's Poet in New York, 3 December 1990 (Box 626, Folder 3)
  - Conversation with Alexander M. Yakolev, 4 December 1990 (Box 626, Folder 4)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts and Letters, 4 December 1990 (Box 626, Folder 5)
  - Dinner celebrating the future of the School of Law, NYU, 6 December 1990 (Box 626, Folder 6)
  - University Senate, NYU, 6 December 1990 (Box 626, Folder 7)
  - Carter-Menil Awards, 10 December 1990 (Box 626, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, 13 December 1990 (Box 626, Folder 11)
  - King Juan Carlos I Professor Lecture, 13 December 1990 (Box 626, Folder 12)
  - USA Today op-ed, 23 December 1990 (Box 626, Folder 13)
  - "The Independent Commission: A Commentary," article published in the American Oxonian, 4 January 1991 (Box 626, Folder 14)
  - Article for NYU Law Review, tribute to Dean Robert B. McKay, 15 January 1991 (Box 626, Folder 15)
  - Remarks delivered upon receiving the first annual Founders Day Award from the NY School for the Deaf, 15 January 1991 (Box 626, Folder 16)
  - Script for a two-minute address on Hellenic culture videotaped by the Greek Archdiocese (NYC), 16 January 1991 (Box 626, Folder 17)
  - Introduction of L. Jay Oliva at a meeting of the Alumni Council, NYU, 16 January 1991 (Box 626, Folder 18)
  - Remarks introducing honorees at the International Rescue Committee Freedom Award Luncheon (NYC), 24 January 1991 (Box 626, Folder 19)
  - "Libraries in a Democratic Society," scheduled to be delivered at a conference on the national library in the life of the nation (Moscow, USSR) (not delivered), Jan 28, 1991 (Box 626, Folder 20)
  - Introduction of Michel Fribourg, La Maison Francaise, NYU, 29 January 1991 (Box 626, Folder 21)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at the Italian Trade Commission Reception, Casa Italiana, NYU, 31 January 1991 (Box 626, Folder 22)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the Institute of Fine Arts Board of Trustees, NYU, 6 February 1991 (Box 626, Folder 23)
  - Remarks scheduled to be delivered at the International Congress on Trade Cooperation and Investment Opportunities in Czechoslovakia (Prague, Czechoslovakia) (not delivered), 7 February 1991 (Box 626, Folder 24)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 14 February 1991 (Box 626, Folder 25)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring Fyodor Burlatsky, NYU, 14 February 1991 (Box 626, Folder 26)
  - "American Science in the 21st Century: Prospects & Problems," William D. Carey Lecture for the American Association for the Advancement of Science (Washington, D.C.), 18 February 1991 (Box 626, Folder 27)
  - Remarks introducing Andrew Athens, the recipient of the Athenagoras Human Rights Award (NYC), 23 February 1991 (Box 626, Folder 28)
  - "Economies in Transition: Management Training & Market Economics Education in Central & Eastern Europe," SEED Lecture (Washington, D.C.), 26 February 1991 (Box 626, Folder 29)
  - Remarks introducing Lew Rudin, recipient of the Metro Center Torch of Learning Award (NYC), 27 February 1991 (Box 626, Folder 30)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Alberto Vitale, Robert Jachino, and the Gallatin Publishing Program, NYU, 27 February 1991 (Box 626, Folder 31)
  - "The American Speakership: The Office in Historical Perspective," book review published in The Review of Politics, 27 February 1991 (Box 626, Folder 32)
  - Remarks delivered at Sunday at the Square, NYU, 3 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 33)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the Medical Center Board of Trustees, NYU, 5 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 34)
  - Brief remarks at a meeting of the United Way/NYU Community Fund, 6 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 35)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon honoring Sir John Pope-Hennessy, NYU, 6 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 36)
  - "America's Unfinished Agenda: The Relationship of Domestic Factors to Foreign Politics," delivered at the French-American Conference (Washington, D.C.), 8 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 37)
  - Remarks delivered at the naming of the Abe Burrows Theater, NYU, 14 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 38)
  - Remarks delivered at the National Book Critics Circle Awards, NYU, 14 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 39)
  - Welcome remarks delivered at the Sixth Annual Federation Finance Forum, NYU, 16 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 40)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the Board of Trustees, NYU, 18 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 41)
  - Fourth Annual Nancy Hanks Lecture (Washington, D.C.), 20 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 42)
  - Presentation of award to Alberto Vitale at the Metro International Fulbright Awards Dinner, 21 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 43)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 21 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 44)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, NYU, 28 March 1991 (Box 626, Folder 45)
  - Remarks delivered before a meeting of the American Academy of Art & Science, NYU, 2 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 46)
  - Remarks honoring Derek Bok at the Harvard Overseers' Farewell Dinner (Boston, MA), 6 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 47)
  - Remarks delivered at a luncheon at the Elite African Women Conference, NYU, 9 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 48)
  - Testimony on employee educational assistance delivered before the Ways & Means Committee of the House of Representatives (Washington, D.C.), 9 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 49)
  - Remarks delivered on receiving the Torch of Excellence award from the School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions, NYU, 10 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 50)
  - Remarks delivered at a meeting of the University Senate, NYU, 11 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 51)
  - Remarks delivered at the Annual Convention of the National School Boards Association (San Francisco, CA), 13 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 52)
  - "The Independent Commission: A Commentary," published in the American Oxonian, 15 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 53)
  - Remarks delivered by Sheldon Solow at a luncheon commemorating the Institute of Fine Arts, NYU, 16 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 54)
  - Introduction of Jimmy Carter on his receiving the Onassis Prize for Man & Society (Athens, Greece), 18 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 55)
  - Talking points for remarks delivered at a CASH luncheon, NYU ), 21 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 56)
  - Remarks delivered at the Founders Day Honors Convocation, NYU, 21 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 57)
  - Introductory remarks preceding a lecture by George Steiner of Churchill College, NYU, 22 April 1991 (Box 626, Folder 58)
  - "Strengthening Education & Domestic Policies in Support of Enlightened United States Leadership Abroad," Kenneth Holland Lecture (NYC), 23 April 1991 (Box 627, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254733
  - Brief remarks delivered at the 25-Year Service Awards, NYU, 24 April 1991 (Box 627, Folder 2)
  - "Higher Education & Adult Learners: Directions for the 90's," delivered at the Kean University Masters Candidates Convocation (Union, NJ), 24 April 1991 (Box 627, Folder 3)
  - Brief remarks at the unveiling of Wagner memorabilia, NYU, 24 April 1991 (Box 627, Folder 4)
  - Remarks delivered at a dinner honoring Secretary Lamar Alexander & Chairman William Ford (Washington, D.C.), 25 April 1991 (Box 627, Folder 5)